<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>street.yoga - Finance</title><link href="https://street.yoga/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://street.yoga/feeds/finance.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://street.yoga/</id><updated>2022-04-24T00:00:00+02:00</updated><subtitle>Yoga &amp; Machines</subtitle><entry><title>Introducing streetyoga.capital</title><link href="https://street.yoga/money%20makes%20the%20world%20go%20round.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-04-24T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2022-04-24T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>streetyogi</name></author><id>tag:street.yoga,2022-04-24:/money makes the world go round.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Financial independence is part of Yoga&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;div class="gist"&gt;
    &lt;script src='https://gist.github.com/037f9a271324524e775e.js?file=Introducing_Streetyoga_Capital.md'&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
    &lt;noscript&gt;
        &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;As time passes by, street.yoga as a company has evolved, and so did I. Yoga will allways be my number one priority, that will never change.  

But what is yoga exactly, or rather yoga darshana? It is the union between mind, body and spirit. I was focused on the spirit and the body,
but neglected my mind.  
I'm still living in the market, allways will. I don't see myself moving to the himalayas and renounce the world, 
renounce all thought and renounce my curiosity.  

One of my passions preceding my yoga passion are computers and programming, and as much as I tried to renounce this passion to focus solely 
on the physical and spiritual aspect of yoga, and tried to still my mind, it didn't work. And why should it? Computers are part of my life,
and every yogi on the internet. And as a yogi you are either willing to renounce that world or you are not. I am not. So today I started a 
new project on github which will satiate my thirst for programming in the Python language.

I will post on my site about computers and yoga interchangeabely.   
The new project I started concerns itself with algorithmic trading on different cryptocurrency exchanges and is located 
at [streetyoga.capital](https://streetyoga.github.io/streetyoga.capital/).  
I'm still open for my yoga business although I always struggled to take money for my services, it never felt right, it never will.

Namaste my dear yogis, and never forget to live by the eight limbs of yoga, even when participating in the market.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><category term="Finance"></category><category term="python"></category><category term="pandas"></category></entry></feed>